《终空》前情提要
Previously on Final Space...
盖瑞和阿瓦卡多鏖战正酣
Gary and Avocato got their butt cheeks in a hot fight.
总司令也马上就要抓到他们了  狗带啦！
The Lord Commander is hot on their trail. Oh, crap!
现在  我们的英雄们齐心协力保护月饼
Now our heroes have joined forces to protect Mooncake
以及救出阿瓦卡多的儿子  小卡多
and save Avocato's son, Little Cato.
他们打算怎么做？他们打算往那藏？
What are they going to do? Where are they going to hide?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
这就是为什么我们要看这一集啊朋友们！
That's why we're watching this episode, y'all!
你还有7分钟氧气可用  盖瑞
You have 7 minutes of oxygen left, Gary.
呼  看啊  是卡尔  卡尔  近来如何？
Phew. Look, it's Carl. Carl, how's life?
卡尔已经死了  盖瑞
Carl is dead, Gary.
该  卡尔  那个混蛋欠我25块钱
Classic Carl. That bastard owes me 25 bucks.
- 求救  求救！   - 你能把声音弄清楚点吗  HUE？
- Mayday, mayday! - Can you clean that up, HUE?
我可以试试  有不少干扰
I can try. There is quite a bit of interference.
- 我们需要帮助！   - 你知道那是谁吗？
- We need help! - Any idea who it is?
不  盖瑞  我不知道
No, Gary. I'm afraid not.
呃  说不定我可以帮...
Well, maybe I can help these...
算了  我还是在这呆着好了
Actually, I'll just chill over here.
鸭嘴兽字幕组出品
翻译 + 专访听译 + 校对 + 压制：Kyl
Final Space - Chapter Three
终空  第一季第三集
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
本字幕仅供学习交流  请于下载后24小时内删除
给你！会有用的
For you! This will help.
这是什么？你是谁？
What is this? Who's there?
你爸就是个懦夫！
Your father is a coward!
我爸会来救我的  等他来的时候
My father will come for me, and he will kill you
如果你还没被我杀死  他就会杀了你  呀！
if I don't first. Yah! Ow.
奎恩  我看起来有什么不同吗？
Quinn, do I look any different?
我应该是有些不同的  因为你面前的这位
I should because you're looking
是整个银河里赏金最高的人
at the most wanted man in the galaxy.
哦  看看这是谁！
Oh, look who it is!
- 阿瓦卡多  来和奎恩打个招呼   - 不要
- Avocato, come say hi to Quinn. - No.
他最近心情不太好  他儿子被绑架了
He's a bit of a grouch, but his son has been kidnapped.
嗯  我知道
Yeah. I know.
总之  有个大新闻！我现在有一只机械手臂了
Anyways, big development! I have a robot arm.
看哪！哦我的天哪！我怎么...
Look at this! Oh, my god! How do I...
啊！啊！哦！
Ahh! Ahh! Oh!
这就是今天我想告诉你的了  有空给我回电  奎恩
I think that's all I have for you today. Uh... give me a call, Quinn.
哦  我差点忘了  再过四天  我就自由了
Oh, I almost forgot. In four days, I'm a free man.
你说等我自由以...
What do you say when I turn...
接近警告  接近警告
Proximity alert. Proximity alert.
盖瑞  总司令的重型火炉舰队
Gary, we are taking fire
正在向我们猛烈开火
from the Lord Commander's heavy incinerators.
抓紧了  我们该怎么办  HUE？
Grab it firm. What do we do, HUE?
正在计算中  我监测到附近有入侵迹象
Calculating. I am detecting an incursion in our proximity.
有什么？
A what?
有个短时虫洞  盖瑞
A temporal worm, Gary.
这是你唯一的选择了
It's your only option.
短时虫洞可以把我们送到过去或者未来
A temporal worm could send us backwards or forwards
时间跨度可以达到上千年  盖瑞
thousands of years in time, Gary.
你确定那是我们的唯一选择？
Are you sure that's the only choice we have?
那就过去吧！
Feed us to it!
哇！
Whoa!
啊！
Aah!
嗯  屁股不错
Mm, pressed hams.
太棒了！
That was wondrous!
你丫能不能行行好
How about covering up that dick situation
- 穿个裤子成吗  天哪   - 时间刚刚好
- you've got going there? Jeez. - In good time.
话说回来  我们现在是什么时候？
Speaking of which, when are we?
高兴了吗？
Happy?
盖瑞  我们穿越到了四天之后
Gary, we have jumped four days into the future.
等等  啥？也就是说我的刑期结束了
Wait. What? That means my last four days of jail are up.
对吗  HUE？芝麻开门！打开我的宝藏吧！
Right, HUE? Open sesame! Unlock my bounty!
有关服刑的第九条规定已经说明
Clause nine of your imprisonment stipulates that all
一切时间相关的干扰不计入刑期
time-related disruptions have zero effect on your sentence.
什么？所以没有巧克力大金币？
What? So no chocolate treasure coins?
你是想说饼干吗  盖瑞？
Are you referring to cookies, Gary?
是的！
Yes!
哦  那就没有
Oh, then no.
过分了  HUE  你过分了！
This is a load, HUE, a load!
听着  盖瑞  我们已经被盯上了
Listen, Gary. We're marked targets,
无论我们藏在什么洞里  总司令一定会
and no matter what hole we hide in, the Lord Commander will
把我们从洞里揪出来  也把月饼从那个洞里夺走
find us in our hole and take Mooncake from that hole.
我知道到处都已经被各种洞洞穿了
I know that's a whole lot of holes,
但我们也掉到麻烦的大洞里了
but we're in a whole lot of trouble.
HUE？
HUE?
阿瓦卡多说的没错
Avocato is correct.
在搞清状况之前  我们先得把他藏起来
We need to hide him until we figure things out.
我知道一个能保护流亡者的地方
Look. I've heard of a place that safeguards fugitives.
最近的一处在雅尔诺  在那里没人能发现他
The closest one is on Yarno. No one will find him there.
HUE  引擎全开  我们去雅尔诺
HUE, spool up the engines. We're going to Yarno.
泰拉·康·普莱姆
18650区
十二秘社
施救者胡拉  我一直很敬重十二秘社
Helper Hula, I've always respected the Order of the 12
因为你们是宇宙之眼
being the eyes of the universe.
告诉我  E-351在哪？！
Where is E-351?!
啊！你快死了！
Ah! You're dying!
快死了？真的吗  大天才？我知道我快死了！
Dying? Really, genius? I know I'm dying!
每次你施展那个光术  你都在加速自己的死亡
Every time you use your light, you quicken your own death.
这就是为什么我需要月饼  那个白痴管它叫这个来着吧
That's why I need Mooncake, or whatever that idiot calls him.
我需要有它才能活下去  告诉我  它在哪
I need him to live. Tell me where he is.
耐心一点
Patience.
这可没帮到我
That wasn't very helpful.
呃
Ugh!
快帮我找到它  不然下次我就不留情了
You will find him for me, or next time I finish the job.
雅尔诺
泥蠔呀！我是泽尔贡·图卡里西  欢迎来到雅尔诺...
Gworplo! I'm Zargon Tukalishi, and welcome to Yarn...
他们似乎给这里做了点变化
Looks like they've made some changes around here.
真想不到  “死亡斗兽场”听起来
You don't say, because the Deathcropolis
还挺像个和谐的教会野餐会啥的
just sounded like a lovely church picnic.
别担心  月饼
Don't worry, Mooncake.
我们能做到的
We got this.
月亮团子  自制的月亮团子
Moonobumps, homemade moonobumps.
哦不错！还有免费发糖的！
Oh, sweet! They're just handing out free candy!
哇  哇啊
Wow. Whoa.
哦  哦  他手里有冰棍！
Oh, oh, he has a Popsicle now!
啊！
Ahh!
我感觉充满了力量！
I feel so replenished.
哦  哇  哦！这又是啥？！
Oh, wow. Oh! Just what is this?!
我的胸怎么支楞出来一个飞镖！
There's a dart sticking out of my chesticles!
你能不能别从外星变态手里拿这些垃圾东西？
Can you not take crap from weird alien skeevoids?
记下来了  “别从外星变态手里拿垃圾”
Noted, "Do not take crap from skeevoids."
- 呃   - 啊！
- Ugh.  - Ahh!
有量子引力干扰
There's a quantum gravitational disturbance
从离木星两个秒差距的地方传出来了
emanating two parsecs from Jupiter.
如果我没算错  我们的生命都...
If my math is right, all our lives might depend...
奎恩  是三烦  别担心  我就在你家
Quinn, it's Triborn. Don't worry. I'm at your place.
一切都还好  但是有一个很不好的消息
Everything is okay, but super bad news.
你不会喜欢的
You're not going to like it.
实际上  我不知道所有的“喜欢”都怎么样了
In fact, I don't know what happened to all the like.
“喜欢”都去了哪呢？
Where did all the like go?
- 快告诉我  别废话！   - 我会告诉你的  没废话
- Tell me, already! - I will tell you, already.
苏比利尔·斯通昨天派出了一架帝国巡飞舰
Superior Stone dispatched an Imperium cruiser
他想要逮捕你
yesterday to apprehend you
因为你违反了很多法令  差不多47条
because you kind of broke a lot of laws, like 47 laws.
你怎么不早点告诉我？！
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
为什么我不早点告诉你？这是个很好的问题  不是吗？
Why didn't I tell you sooner? That is the question, isn't it?
答案是  我很忙的
The answer, I've been busy.
你在动我的东西吗？
Are you touching my stuff?
我为什么要动你的东西
Why would I be touching your stuff.
它让我变得梦幻般的漂亮
It makes me look so dreamy and beautiful.
我绝不动你的漂亮的东西
I would never be touching your beautiful stuff.
奎恩  帝国巡飞舰正在向你靠近
Quinn, an Imperium cruiser is closing in on your position.
- 就是这里  盖瑞   - 是这里？
- This is the place, Gary. - This is the place?
这里  就在这  就是你说的地方？
This, right here, is the place?
我可不下去
I'm not going down there.
朋友们  欢迎来到十二秘社雅尔诺分会...
Welcome, friends, to the Order of 12 Yarno chapter...
一个代表马上会和你们见面
a representative will meet you shortly.
- 我能...   - 天哪！
- How can I... - Jeez!
...帮你吗？
...help?
- 你吓到我了   - 你是施救者之一吗？
- You got me. - Are you a helper?
哦  不是  我是施救者的帮手
Oh, no. I assist the helpers.
所以你是施救者的施救者？
So you're a helper-helper?
我会告诉他  你们已经到了
I will tell him you have... arrived.
那个家伙直直地穿墙过去了
Guy straight up ghosted through that wall.
- 接受事实吧   - 难以接受  那个家伙
- Live with it. - I can't. The guy just ghosted
- 穿墙过去了  老兄  啊！   - 我能帮你吗？
- through that wall, yo. Ahh! - How can I help?
- 我们很乐意帮你们   - 谢了
- We love to help. - Thanks.
我们需要给这个小东西找个安全的地方
Well, we need to find a safe place for my little buddy.
抱歉  我们满员了
Sorry. We're at capacity.
哦！
Oh!
不过我们总可以硬挤进去一个的
But we could always squeeze in one more.
- 这是个如此珍贵的样本   - 嗯
- Such a precious specimen. - Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
你... 你能别这么瘆人吗？
C-Can you say that just a little less creepy-like?
好的  我猜不行
Okay. I guess not.
月饼
Mooncake.
Chookity?
不会离开太久的  好吗？
No one's saying goodbye, here. Okay?
我会尽快回来的
I'll be back as soon as I can.
只是暂时分别  我保证
It's only temporary. I promise.
Chookity pok.
盖瑞  他会没事的  他自己能照顾自己
Gary, he'll be fine. He can take care of himself.
顺便一提  我还不知道你的名字  你是...
By the way, I never got your name, mister...
- 斯蒂魔   - 哇啊！
- Stevil. - Whoa!
哇哇哇哇哇  停一下
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Pump the breaks.
好吧  这家伙名字里就带个“魔”字
Okay. The freaking guy has "evil" in his name.
我可不把月饼交到斯蒂魔手里
I'm not handing Mooncake over to a guy freaking named Stevil!
- 斯蒂魔有点吓人   - 确实有点吓人！
- Stevil is a bit alarming. - It is a bit alarming!
我们只是想帮忙啊！
We only want to help!
阿瓦卡多  咱们换地吧
Avocato, let's find another place.
- 走吧   - 留步！
- Let's go. - Stop!
成吧  这已经是报丧女妖级别的吓人了！
Okay. This is full-blown banshee screech, alarming!
报丧女妖（banshee）：爱尔兰神话中的女性精灵，通常被认为是死亡的象征。
- 月饼！   - 睡吧
- Mooncake! - Sleep.
通知最高施救者胡拉  我们帮了大忙了
Alert High Helper Hula we have been most helpful.
斯蒂魔深刻诠释了“魔”的本质！
Stevil lived right up to the evil in his name!
看哪！我们到了超级安全的忘却游乐园了
Look! We made it to the super safe oblivion amusement park
可惜里面有没完没了的超级不安全的台阶！
of never-ending unsafe stairs!
太好玩了！谢了  阿瓦卡多
What fun! Thanks, Avocato.
这是拉撒路陷阱
It's a Lazarus trap.
只有陷阱大师才能做出这样的陷阱
Only master trap-makers can make these,
或者是特别喜欢台阶的人
and people who really like stairs.
至少我们还没陷进岩浆湖之类的东西里
At least we're not sinking into, like, a lake of lava or something.
听我说  我们脑子里想到的所有东西都会变成真的  听到了吗？
Listen to me. Anything we think of becomes reality. Okay?
我听到了  所以我们得想点好的
Right. Okay. So we've got to think positive.
哦  哦！饼干！
Ooh, ooh! Cookies!
- 不！   - 嘿！
- No! - Hey!
吃了我吧！我很好吃的！我是饼干啊！
Eat me! I'm delicious! I'm a cookie!
什么？我可没想什么
What? It's not like I'm imagining
会杀人的凶残零食啊？
murderous killing confections?
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
对于今天死亡斗兽场的献祭
Everybody is super excited
所有人都无比激动
about today's sacrifices at the Deathcropolis.
哦！
Ooh!
但你可不是祭品
But you're not being sacrificed.
总司令需要你
The Lord Commander needs you.
他在干什么？
What is he doing?
Chookity pok!
奎恩·厄尔冈  我们奉命
Quinn Airgone, we have orders to arrest you
以偷窃航空设备罪逮捕你
for aerial grand theft.
- 查克？   - 是的  我是查克
- Chuck? - Yes. This is Chuck.
请马上投降  然后这些就都当没发生
Now, please surrender, and this all goes away.
听着  混蛋  没门
Listen, jerk nuts. No.
她刚是管我叫混蛋了吗？
Did she just call me jerk nuts?
哦  好吧  好的... 好的  你马上就要被逮捕了
Oh. Okay, yeah... Yeah. I think you are under arrest.
嘿！死王八蛋  我可不会被抓住
Hey! Douche canoe, not happening.
老天啊  你说  “死王八蛋”
God. You said, "Douche canoe."
好的  听好了  奎恩...
All right. Listen, Quinn...
不  你听好了
No. You listen.
我正在拯救世界
I'm trying to save the world, here.
希望你们调转舰头
So you're going to turn your vessel around
假装从来没看到过我
and forget you ever saw me.
- 老兄  你在哭吗？   - 不  不  我没在哭
- Dude, are you crying? - No. No, I'm not crying.
是太空花粉过敏
It's space pollen.
啊啊啊！你没说“请”！
Ah, ah, ah! Didn't say the magic word!
啊！为啥只有我被饼干缠住了？
Aaah! Why am I the only one covered in cookies?
- 你咋没有饼干！   - 盖瑞  别再想饼干了！
- You have no cookies! - Gary, de-think the cookies!
不知道我能不能做到  我想象力太丰富了
Not sure that's possible. I'm a very creative guy.
如果它们有激光眼  岂不是很酷？
Like, wouldn't it be cool if they had, like, laser eyes?
啊！跑啊！
Aah! Run!
- 哦我的天哪！   - 想点别的东西！
- Oh, my God! - Think of something else!
- 什么东西都行！   - 比如三叉戟？
- Anything else! - What, like tridents?
- 不！不！   - 耶！酷！
- No! No! - Yeah! Yes!
不！别想三叉戟！
No! Not like tridents!
我满脑子都是挥着三叉戟的
I'm thinking about little trident-wielding
激光眼小饼干！
laser-shooting death cookies!
我什么都不想  什么都不想  什么都不想
I'm thinking of nothing, nothing, nothing.
哦！哇！哦！哦  我的天哪
Oh! Whoa! Oh! Oh, my gosh.
- 我要把你的眼睛吃了   - 然后在你眼窝里撒尿！
- I'm going to eat your eyes out. - And pee in your sockets!
你们永远逃不出这里的
You're never going to leave this place.
为什么那个独狼饼干在边上？
Why is that one cookie lone-wolfing it across the edge?
哦！他跳起来了！哇！像个天使一样！
Oh! He's leaping! Whoa! He's like an angel!
- 哦  我的天哪...   - 我要杀了你！
- Oh, my God... - I'm going to kill you!
他在戳我的眼睛啊！
It's stabbing my eyes!
Ohh.
Chookity pok!
谨以死者  致以生者！
To the ones who live for the ones who die!
这不公平  我一直是个好人
It's not fair. I've been good.
我乐于助人
I help people.
我很有耐心  特别特别有耐心！
I've been patient, unbelievably patient!
哦  总司令！我把药拿来了，大人！
Oh, Lord Commander! I brought your medicine, sir!
旁边还有一块小饼干
I put a little biscuit on the side,
只送给你  我特别的小王子
just for you, my special little prince.
- 这是什么？   - 呃！啊！
- What is this? - Ugh! Gah!
我喜欢更小的小饼干
I like the much littler kind of biscuits.
我和你说过了  艾瑞克
I have told you this, Eric.
我和你说过了！
I told you this!
我们帮了大忙了
We have been most helpful.
我们找到了月饼
We have found Mooncake.
我的耐心有了回报
My patience paid off.
你杀得越多
The more you kill,
十二泰坦就越欢喜
the more the Twelve Titans beyond rejoice.
盖瑞  我们得醒过来  闭上眼
Gary, we need to wake up. Close your eyes.
你让我闭着眼醒来？
You want me to wake up by closing my eyes?
- 这根本没道理！   - 这里的一切都没道理！
- That doesn't make any sense! - Nothing makes any sense in here!
好吧  你说的有道理  我闭上眼了
All right. Good point. Okay. I'm closing my eyes.
不管用
It's not working.
- 你好  盖瑞   - 奎恩？
- Hi, Gary. - Quinn?
好久不见
It's been a long time.
- 快来  我想你了   - 真的是你？
- Come here. I missed you. - Is it really you?
再近点
Closer.
- 盖瑞...   - 给我滚开！
- Gary... - Get off me!
这是陷阱的一部分
It's part of the trap.
盖瑞  别听他的
Gary, don't listen to him.
你得相信我  她不是真的
You need to trust me. She isn't real.
我们一起回家吗  爸爸？
Are we going home, dad?
相信我  伙计  咱们都得醒过来
Trust me, buddy. We both need to wake up.
我不想醒过来
I don't want to wake up.
那你可得忍一下这个了
Then you're really not going to want this.
出来了！我救了咱俩
We're out! I saved us.
- 不  是我救了你   - 我也救了你
- No, I saved you. - And I, you.
- 你可没救我   - 我明明救了
- No, you didn't. - But I did.
- 你差点让咱俩送命  盖瑞   - 那咱们扯平了
- You almost got us killed, Gary. - Then we're even.
咱们得去找月饼！
We've got to find Mooncake!
盖瑞  我告诉过你月饼会没事的
Gary, I told you Mooncake is going to be okay.
- 他是个超级武器   - 错！
- He's a super weapon. - Wrong!
小绿球球朋友  明明是纯良无害的爱之糖球！
Little green ball friend is a harmless gumball of love!
HUE  你在吗？
HUE, you there?
你去哪了  盖瑞？
Where have you been, Gary?
解释起来都太离奇了
It would sound too insane to even explain.
你能锁定月饼的位置吗？
Can you lock into Mooncake's location?
- 啊！   - 呃  盖瑞？
- Ugh! - Uh, Gary?
小家伙
Little buddy.
最后的祭品即将登场
The final sacrifice awaits.
杀啊！杀啊！杀啊！杀啊！
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
你好啊月饼  我找你找得好苦
Hello, Mooncake. I have been looking all over for you.
别害羞嘛
Don't be shy.
快来打个招呼
Come in and say hello.
啊！
Rahh!
我怎么变得这么虚弱？
How did I become so weak?
月饼！
Mooncake!
Doot, doot, doot, doot!
Chookity!
哦！
Oh!
- 盖瑞！   - 一切都结束了  那个盖瑞
- Gary! - It's over, The Gary.
是“盖瑞”  只有“盖瑞”
"Gary." It's just "Gary."
你到底想干啥  老兄？别来烦我们了好不好？
What is your deal, dude? Why won't you just leave us alone?
你根本不明白吧？
You have no idea, do you?
月饼是个钥匙
Mooncake is the key.
那个东西能开启终空的大门
That being can unlock Final Space.
终空又他喵的是啥？
What the mother-loving crap is Final Space?
那就不关你事了  要玩个游戏吗  盖瑞？
That's my business. Should we play a game, Gary?
我爱玩游戏  我总会赢
I love games. I always win.
你知道我想要什么  我...
You know what I want, and I...
Ya!
哦！我！的！天！哪！
Oh, my gosh!
格兰多的手套啊！
Sweet Grandor's glove!
你真的是个毁灭行星的超级武器！
You are a planet-destroying super weapon!
Chookity!
哇！好极了！
Whoa! Yes!
太太太太太棒了！
That's so freaking tight!
- 游戏可不是这么玩的！   - 那  这么玩呢？
- That's not how we play the game! - How about this game?
- 啊  你失手了   - 擦  把锁射开！
- Ah, you missed. - Freak. Shoot for the locks!
- 盖瑞  小心！   - 呃！
- Gary, look out! - Ugh!
啊！呃
Ah! Ugh.
我来救你了  盖瑞！我来救你了！
I'm going to save you, Gary! I'm saving you!
我是来救你的  盖瑞！我救你脱离苦海了
I'm here to save you, Gary! The day is saved.
去你的KVN！我恨你！
Freaking KVN! I hate you so much!
我真的等不及你死的那一天了！
I truly can't wait for the day you die!
哦  我的天哪  到时候谁都不会为你伤心的
Oh, my gosh. No one will be sad.
大家都会乐疯了的！
There will only be happiness!
- 嘿盖瑞！   - 别  别来这一套
- Hey, Gary! - Don't even. Just don't even.
KVN拯救了一切
KVN has saved everything.
引力干扰太强了
The gravitational disturbance, it's massive
它还在加强... 加强了很多...很多很多
and growing... a lot... a lot, a lot.
这就是我之前想告诉你的
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
探测器即将失效  探测器即将失效
Probe failure imminent. Probe failure imminent.
我们需要马上离开这里
We need to get out of here right now.
哦天哪！启动尾部推进器！
Oh, God! Engage rear thrusters!
- 啊啊啊！   - 啊！
- Ahh! - Ah!
我不是死王八蛋！啊！
I am not a douche canoe! Ahh!
啊！
Ahh!
紧急求救  紧急求救！我是奎恩·厄尔冈
Mayday, mayday! This is Quinn Airgone.
有人能听到吗？请来救我！
Can someone hear me? Help me!
我按你的要求扫描了所有
I've processed your scan of all prisoner
转移出泰拉·康·普莱姆的囚犯
transfers out of Tera Con Prime.
他们之中并没有小卡多
There is no match for Little Cato.
月饼？
Mooncake?
怎么了  小家伙？
What's wrong, bud?
Mm.
我懂了  你一个嘴炮射出了死亡射线
I get it. So you shoot a murder beam out of your face hole.
那又怎么了？它可能发生在我们绝大多数人的身上
So what? I mean, it happens to the best of us.
你知道吗  某天我吃了个超级辣的玉米卷饼
I mean, just the other day I had a burrito,
你真该看看我射出的死亡射线
and you should have saw the freaking murder beam
只不过那是从我的屁...
that came out of my ba...
总之你懂的  仔细想想的话
And, you know, it's actually pretty sweet,
其实还挺有意思的
if you think about it.
我只是想告诉你  刚刚发生的事不会改变
I mean, I just want you to know that that doesn't change
- 你和这个家伙之间的感情   - 我？
- anything between you and this guy. - Me?
不是你！
Not you!
Chookity!
是这个人
Him.
你的能力并没有把你变成坏人
It doesn't make you the bad guy.
真的没有  这种能力
It really doesn't. I mean, it makes the scum
只会让想把你当武器用的人变成坏人
who want to use you as the weapon the bad guy.
你是个好人  是个大好人
Look, you're a good guy to the max core.
Ohh!
我不会再离开你了
I'm never going to let you go again.
我现在明白了  我唯一放心敢把你交出去的人
I now know the only one I can trust with you
只有伟大的本王啊
is my own awesomeness.
Mm!
我开始喜欢上这一切了
I'm starting to like these.
Mm.
盖瑞  我收到一条紧急求救消息
Gary, I am receiving a mayday call.
紧急求救  紧急求救！我是奎恩·厄尔冈！
Mayday, mayday! This is Quinn Airgon!
有人能听到吗？请来救我！
Can someone hear me? Help me!
哦我的老天啊  是奎恩
Oh, my crap. It's Quinn.
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
幕后专访
INSIDE THE EPISODE
我们在这部动画里想做的一件事就是
One thing we wanted to do in the series was
让总司令成为一个真正的威胁
kind of make Lord Commander a genuine threat.
一个真正卑鄙无耻的小人
you know, this is a real meanness,
这就是我们的机会  我们陈明了
this was our chance to do a show now to establish of
总司令是个大坏蛋  一个真真正正的坏人
this guy is our big bad, also legitimately bad.
我说不上来我是怎么想到那些
You know, I couldn't really tell you why I came up with
拿着三叉戟  发射着激光的死亡饼干的
the trident-wielding shooting-laser death cookies.
这个想法合乎逻辑地出现在了剧本里  看上去也挺搞笑的
I think it just logically came up into the script, and it seemed really funny.
我们弄出来一个短时虫洞  只是因为
The whole creation of the temporal worm was just kind of
想模仿一下虫洞  然后里面有个虫子
the idea of a wormhole, you got a worm in there.
在这我们没想太多  就是个虫子啊
There's not a lot of thought in there, just the worm.
在随后的剧情里  你们会知道
Oh yeah, I mean, something you gonna find out later on in the actual show is
月饼从何而来  以及盖瑞和月饼之间有哪些联系
where Mooncake comes from, but also the connection between him and Mooncake
月饼超级厉害  没人打得过月饼
Mooncake is a champion yo. Nobody can beat Mooncake.